muzikair.com 2017-07-09

# Privacy Policy | Classical for all | MUZIK Air

  * HOME
  * Privacy Policy

MUZIK Air is an online platform run by MUZIK CREATIVE DIGITAL LTD., which provides classical music combined with technology and internet social networking service. We respect our members' privacy very much. The following “Privacy Policy” will help our members to learn more about how MUZIK Air collects, uses and protects our members' personal information.

### Collecting members' personal information

1.When a member signs up to be a MUZIK-Air's member, we ask the member to provide a username, email address, profile picture, nick name, gender, birth date, educational background, category of employment, and annual income.

2.When a member uses the Q & A system, we will ask the member to provide email address, so we can provide instant and accurate information for the said member.

### Use of members' personal information

1.The personal information collected by our website will only be used for identification purposes. Without the consent of our members, we will not use the collected personal information for any other use nor will we share the information with any third party, and the third party will not be authorized to use the said information.

2.When a member may have violated our terms of service, caused any damage to our website or other members, or when we have been requested by judiciary authority to disclose certain member's personal information due to public safety, we shall disclose or read the said member's personal information under legal procedure.

### Autonomy of members' personal information

1\. MUZIK Air lets the members to keep their autonomy to provide their personal information. When a member agrees and signs up to be our member, the member has the right to decide whether to provide us with his/her personal information for our use.

2.MUZIK Air provides our members the right to look up, revise, delete the recorded personal information, and decide whether to receive email notifications of relevant activities.

### The safety of members' personal information

1.In order to protect our members' privacy, we use SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) of So-Net online payment solution in certain circumstances to ensure the safety when transmitting users' personal information. We ask our members to secure their password and personal information safely. Also, we kindly remind our members to log out or close the window after using MUZIK Air's relevant services to keep their personal information from being usurped.

2\. Please be noted that MUZIK Air's relevant websites may contain links to other websites, which may collect personal information as well. Despite of the content of the said websites' privacy policy, MUZIK Air is not related to and does not have joint responsibility to the said websites.

### Use and collection of other information

1\. We record our members' IP address and their activities when surfing on MUZIK Air for the following use only:

Analyzing our members' preferences and habits, collecting and calculating traffic and network flow, adjusting our website's content based on our members' preferences and behaviors. Please be assured that we will not correspond the aforesaid information to our members' personal information.

2\. We keep all the rights of collecting and analyzing all information related to users' behaviors.

### Changes to privacy policy

MUZIK Air has the right to revise this “Privacy Policy”. When we make major revision, we will notify via our official website or newsletter regarding relevant matters.
